Alexander Fernandez

Full Stack Developer



- ♥ Villa Crespo, 1414 Buenos Aires, Argentina
 - alex97l@hotmail.com
 - **♦** 01121635165 **▶** Portfolio
- iii 26/02/1997 ► Argentinian **©** Single
 - in Linkedin 🖸 Github

Profile

Innovative and deadline-driven full stack developer with 1 year of experience designing and developing user-centered websites from initial concept to final.

Skills

Html / Css / Javascript (Jsx / Scss), Ruby on Rails (Ruby / Irb), Databases (Sql / PostgreSQL), React (Node / Express / Redux), Package managers (Yarn / Npm), Testing (Enzyme / Jest)

Courses

React course, *Udemy* ☑ 2022 – 2022 | Remote

Full Stack developer, Le Wagon ☑ 2021 – 2022 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Professional Experience

Freelancer

2022 – present | Buenos Aires, Argentina

In charge of Marketing & Supplies, Coto Cicsa

2017 - 2022 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

- I started as a cadet then was promoted and got in charge of shipments;
- Managed up to 234 shipments at the same time
- Consulted by clients when they had any trouble.
- Managed to lead 15 employees. In the third year, I was in charge of the marketing and supply section.

Education

International Relations, *Siglo XXI* 2021 – present | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Software Engineer, UBA

2017 - 2020 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Languages	
Spanish	
English	